Lewis W. Douglas papers, 1859-1974 (bulk 1880-1960)
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Series IV: Lewis W. Douglas Papers, 1906-1974
  - Subseries II: State Legislature and Congress, 1923-1933
    - 70th Congress, Administration, 1927-1929
      - Department of the Interior, Bureau of Indian Affairs (Indian School Survey). 1929 (Box 128, Folder 2)
      - Department of the Interior, Bureau of Indian Affairs, general. no date (Box 128, Folder 3)
      - Department of the Interior, Bureau of Pensions, miscellaneous and individual cases. no date (Box 128, Folder 4-5)
      - Department of the Interior, General Land Office, general. no date (Box 128, Folder 6)
      - Department of the Interior, General Land Office, homesteads. no date (Box 128, Folder 7)
      - Department of the Interior, General Land Office, Ivanhoe Copper Company Case. 1927 (Box 128, Folder 8)
      - Department of the Interior, General Land Office, oil and gas permits. no date (Box 128, Folder 9)
      - Department of the Interior, Bureau of Reclamation. no date (Box 129, Folder 1)
      - Department of the Interior, Geological Survey. no date (Box 129, Folder 2)
      - Department of the Interior, National Park Service. no date (Box 129, Folder 3)
      - Civil Service Commission. no date (Box 129, Folder 4)
      - Federal Radio Commission. no date (Box 129, Folder 5)
      - General and Special Claims Commission. no date (Box 129, Folder 6)
      - Intersate Commerce Commission. no date (Box 129, Folder 7)
      - U.S. Geographic Board. no date (Box 129, Folder 8)
      - Miscellaneous offices. no date (Box 129, Folder 9)
      - President's messages and addresses. no date (Box 129, Folder 10)
      - Miscellaneous speeches from the 69th and 70th Congresses. no date (Box 129, Folder 11)
      - Miscellaneous clippings. no date (Box 129, Folder 12)
      - Invitations. January 1927-March 1929 (Box 129, Folder 13-14)
    - 70th Congress, Legislation, 1927-1929
      - Calendars and History of Legislation of the House of Representatives, 70th Congress. December 5, 1927-March 4, 1929 (Box 130)
      - LWD, 70th Congress, Legislative Record. no date (Box 130, Folder 1)
      - LWD's Bills. no date (Box 130, Folder 2-35)
      - Carl Hayden and Henry F. Ashurst, 70th Congress, Legislative Record. no date (Box 130, Folder 36)
      - Background: 66-69th Congresses. no date (Box 131, Folder 1)
      - Background: 69th Congress (H.R. 9826). no date (Box 131, Folder 2)
      - Background: 69th Congress (S. 3331). no date (Box 131, Folder 3)
      - Various Bills regarding Colorado River Legislation. no date (Box 131, Folder 4)
      - Senator H. Johnson's Bill, S. 728. no date (Box 131, Folder 5)
      - Representative P. Swing's Bill, H.R. 5773. no date (Box 131, Folder 6)
      - H.R. 5773. no date (Box 131, Folder 7)
      - H.R. 5773 (minority reports). no date (Box 131, Folder 8)
      - H.R. 5773 (amendments proposed by McCluskey). no date (Box 131, Folder 9)
      - Correspondence, general. March 1927-March 1929 (Box 132, Folder 1-10)
      - Correspondence, American Legion. no date (Box 133, Folder 1)
      - Correspondence, Arizona Governors, G.W.P. Hunt and J.C. Phillips. no date (Box 133, Folder 2)
      - Correspondence, James S. Casey. no date (Box 133, Folder 3)
      - Correspondence, Colorado River Fact-Finding Committee of Utah. no date (Box 133, Folder 4)
      - Correspondence, Fred T. Colter. no date (Box 133, Folder 5)
      - Correspondence, Carl Hayden. no date (Box 133, Folder 6)
      - Correspondence, John P. Hogan. no date (Box 133, Folder 7)
      - Correspondence, O.C. Merrill, Fedral Power Commission). no date (Box 133, Folder 8)
      - Correspondence, W.C. Mullendore. no date (Box 133, Folder 9)
      - Correspondence, Gifford Pinchot. no date (Box 133, Folder 10)
      - Correspondence, G.E.P. Smith. no date (Box 133, Folder 11)
      - Correspondence, Phil D. Swing. no date (Box 133, Folder 12)
      - Correspondence, Roy O. West, Secretary of the Interior. no date (Box 133, Folder 13)
      - Correspondence, Earl Wheeler. no date (Box 133, Folder 14)
      - Correspondence, Mulford Winsor. no date (Box 133, Folder 15)
      - Correspondence, Replies to LWD's letter to Congressmen, enclosing his minority report on H.R. 5773. no date (Box 133, Folder 16)
      - Petitions and Resolutions. no date (Box 133, Folder 17)
      - Colorado River, hearings before House Committee on Irrigation & Reclamation. January 1928 (Box 134, Folder 1)
      - Colorado River, hearing before House Committee on Rules. April 1928 (Box 134, Folder 2)
      - Colorado River, LWD's speeches and statements. no date (Box 134, Folder 3)
      - Colorado River, material and notes on costs and power. no date (Box 134, Folder 4)
      - Colorado River, material and notes on flood control. no date (Box 134, Folder 5)
      - Colorado River, miscellaneous material. no date (Box 134, Folder 6)
      - Colorado River, LWD's article. no date (Box 134, Folder 7)
      - Colorado River, clippings. August 1927-February 1929 (Box 135, Folder 1-3)
      - Colorado River clippings. 1928 (Box 135, Folder 4)
      - Colorado River, articles and publications. no date (Box 135, Folder 5)
      - Colorado River, Federal Power Commission Publications and Reports. no date (Box 135, Folder 6)
      - Colorado River, speeches. no date (Box 136, Folder 1)
      - Colorado River, Reports: Durand, W.E. no date (Box 136, Folder 2)
      - Colorado River, Reports: Jakobsen, B.F. no date (Box 136, Folder 3)
      - Colorado River, Reports: Levering, J.H. no date (Box 136, Folder 4)
      - Colorado River, Reports: Malone, G.W. no date (Box 136, Folder 5)
      - Colorado River, Reports: various. no date (Box 136, Folder 6)
      - Colorado River, Port of New York Authority. no date (Box 136, Folder 7)
      - Colorado River Development: Colorado River Investigations, water storage and power development, Grand Canyon to the Imperial Valley. Presented by Mr. Oddie. December 10, 1928 (Box 136)
      - 5 miscellaneous printed items regarding aspects ofthe "controversy" in the U.S. Supreme Court. no date (Box 136)
      - Irrigation, Columbia Basin Project. no date (Box 137, Folder 1)
      - Irrigation, Coolidge Dam and San Carlos Project (bills, laws, etc.). no date (Box 137, Folder 2)
      - Irrigation, Coolidge Dam and San Carlos Project, correspondence. 1927-1929 (Box 137, Folder 3-4)
      - Irrigation, Coolidge Dam and San Carlos Project (notes and miscellaneous material). no date (Box 137, Folder 5)
      - Irrigation, Mississippi Flood Control, correspondence. no date (Box 137, Folder 6)
      - Irrigation, Mississippi Flood Control (bills and miscellaneous material). no date (Box 137, Folder 7)
      - Irrigation, Yuma Auxiliary Project and Yuma-Mesa Project. no date (Box 137, Folder 8)
      - Irrigation, Water Rights on the Upper Gila. no date (Box 137, Folder 9)
      - Revenue bill, correspondence. no date (Box 138, Folder 1)
      - Revenue bill (bills and miscellaneous material). no date (Box 138, Folder 2)
      - Roads, paving International Street, Nogales, AZ. no date (Box 138, Folder 3-4)
      - Roads, street in Phoenix, AZ. no date (Box 138, Folder 5)
      - Roads, miscellaneous legislation. no date (Box 138, Folder 6)
      - Roads, federal aid (bills, hearings, general correspondence). no date (Box 138, Folder 7)
      - Roads, federal aid (Arizona roads). no date (Box 138, Folder 8)
      - Roads, federal aid (Arizona Legislature Memorials). no date (Box 138, Folder 9)
      - Tariff, general correspondence and miscellaneous material. no date (Box 139, Folder 1)
      - Tariff, cattle and hides. no date (Box 139, Folder 2)
      - Tariff, cotton. January 30, 1929 (Box 139, Folder 3)
      - Tariff, cotton (correspondence). no date (Box 139, Folder 4)
      - Tariff, cotton (hearings and miscellaneous material). no date (Box 139, Folder 5)
      - Tariff, oils and fats. no date (Box 139, Folder 6)
      - Tariff, ores and metals. no date (Box 139, Folder 7)
      - Tariff, sugar. no date (Box 139, Folder 8)
      - Tariff, miscellaneous commodities. no date (Box 139, Folder 9)
      - Tariff Readjustment. 1929 (Box 139)
      - Tariff, Agricultural Products (general correspondence). no date (Box 140, Folder 1)
      - Tariff, Agricultural Products (general hearings). no date (Box 140, Folder 2)
      - Tariff, Agricultural Products (tomatoes correspondence). no date (Box 140, Folder 3)
      - Tariff, Agricultural Products (tomatoes, U.S. Tariff Commission Statement). no date (Box 140, Folder 4)
      - Tariff, Agricultural Products (tomatoes, U.S. Tariff Commission minutes). no date (Box 140, Folder 5-7)
      - Muscle Shoals Propositions, hearings before the Committee on Military Affairs. February 9-March 13, 1922 (Box 141)
      - Muscle Shoals (background from 68-69th Congresses). no date (Box 141, Folder 1)
      - Muscle Shoals (bills, reports, etc.). no date (Box 141, Folder 2)
      - Muscle Shoals (correspondence and miscellaneous material). no date (Box 141, Folder 3)
      - Public Lands (various bills). no date (Box 141, Folder 4)
      - Public Lands (patents for lands containing minerals). no date (Box 141, Folder 5)
      - Immigration (bills, hearings). no date (Box 142, Folder 1)
      - Immigration, correspondence. no date (Box 142, Folder 2)
      - Immigration (miscellaneous material). no date (Box 142, Folder 3)
      - Military Affairs (promotion, retirement, pay). no date (Box 142, Folder 4)
      - Military Affairs (various). no date (Box 142, Folder 5)
      - Post Office (employees). no date (Box 143, Folder 1)
      - Post Office (postal rates and stamps). no date (Box 143, Folder 2)
      - Post Office (stamped envelopes). no date (Box 143, Folder 3)
      - Prohibition (bills and correspondence). no date (Box 143, Folder 4)
      - Prohibition (miscellaneous material). no date (Box 143, Folder 5)
      - Veterans, correspondence. no date (Box 143, Folder 6)
      - Veterans (compensation for service-connected disabilities). no date (Box 143, Folder 7)
      - Veterans, Emergency Officers' Retirement (bills, speeches, etc). no date (Box 143, Folder 8)
      - Veterans, Emergency Officers' Retirement (correspondence). no date (Box 143, Folder 9)
      - Veterans (hospitals and hospitalization). no date (Box 143, Folder 10)
      - Veterans (insurance). no date (Box 143, Folder 11)
      - Veterans (pensions). no date (Box 143, Folder 12)
      - Farm Relief (bills and correspondence). no date (Box 144, Folder 1)
      - Farm Relief (speeches). no date (Box 144, Folder 2)
      - Farm Relief (miscellaneous material). no date (Box 144, Folder 3)
      - "Burton Embargo," H.J.R. 183 (bills and miscellaneous material). no date (Box 144, Folder 4)
      - "Burton Embargo," H.J.R. 183 (correspondence). no date (Box 144, Folder 5)
      - National Defense (Navy Program). no date (Box 144, Folder 6)
      - National Defense (universal draft). no date (Box 144, Folder 7)
      - National Defense (miscellaneous). no date (Box 144, Folder 8)
      - Beck Election case. no date (Box 145, Folder 1)
      - Bollworm. no date (Box 145, Folder 2)
      - Bridge at Parker, AZ. no date (Box 145, Folder 3)
      - Census. no date (Box 145, Folder 4)
      - Civil Service, Welch Salary Bill (H.R. 6518). no date (Box 145, Folder 5)
      - Civil Service, Retirement Bill. no date (Box 145, Folder 6)
      - Civil Service, Miscellaneous Bills. no date (Box 145, Folder 7)
      - Cotton. no date (Box 145, Folder 8)
      - Courts and the Administration of Justice. no date (Box 145, Folder 9)
      - Deficiency Bills. no date (Box 145, Folder 10)
      - Federal Power Commission Permits. no date (Box 145, Folder 11)
      - Forestry. no date (Box 146, Folder 1)
      - Health, Education, and Welfare. no date (Box 146, Folder 2)
      - Indian Affairs. no date (Box 146, Folder 3)
      - Indian Affairs. no date (Box 146, Folder 4)
      - Interior Department, Appropriations Bill. no date (Box 146, Folder 5)
      - Interstate Commerce. no date (Box 146, Folder 6)
      - Oil and gas permits. no date (Box 146, Folder 7)
      - Ouachita National Park, Kansas. no date (Box 146, Folder 8)
      - Public Health. no date (Box 146, Folder 9)
      - Railroads. no date (Box 147, Folder 1)
      - Sunday Day of Rest, Washington, D.C. no date (Box 147, Folder 2)
      - Treaties. no date (Box 147, Folder 3)
      - War Claims. no date (Box 147, Folder 4)
      - Miscellaneous legislation, A-E. no date (Box 147, Folder 5)
      - Miscellaneous legislation, F-O. no date (Box 147, Folder 6)
      - Miscellaneous legislation, P-Q. no date (Box 147, Folder 7)
      - Miscellaneous legislation, R-Z. no date (Box 147, Folder 8)
    - Political Campaign, 1928
      - The Campaign Book of the Democratic Party, Candidates and Issues in 1928. 1928 (Box 148)
      - Republican Campaign Text-Book. 1928 (Box 148)
      - Correspondence. 1928 (Box 148, Folder 1-3)
      - Correspondence & Press releases (Democratic National Committee). no date (Box 148, Folder 4)
      - Correspondence (Franklin D. Roosevelt). November 29, 1928 (Box 148, Folder 5)
      - Campaign Advertising. no date (Box 148, Folder 6)
      - Campaign Expenses; Certificate of Election. no date (Box 148, Folder 7)
      - Clippings. no date (Box 148, Folder 8)
      - Miscellaneous material (election information, speaking dates, speeches of Ashurts and Hayden). no date (Box 148, Folder 9)
      - Election Returns. no date (Box 148, Folder 10)
      - Correspondence. 1929 (Box 148, Folder 11)
    - 71st Congress, Administration, 1929-1931
      - Voting and attendance records. no date (Box 149, Folder 1)
      - Congressional Committees; Speaker of the House. no date (Box 149, Folder 2)
      - President's messages and addresses. no date (Box 149, Folder 3)
      - Governor Franklin D. Roosevelt. no date (Box 149, Folder 4)
      - Requests for USDA publications. no date (Box 149, Folder 5)
      - Requests for various government publications. no date (Box 149, Folder 6-7)
      - Requests for information. no date (Box 149, Folder 8)
      - Requests, miscellaneous. no date (Box 149, Folder 9)
      - Various publications received and sent. no date (Box 149, Folder 10)
      - Congressional Record mailing list. no date (Box 149, Folder 11)
      - Job requests. no date (Box 149, Folder 12)
      - Correspondence, general. no date (Box 150, Folder 1-2)
      - Correspondence, office. no date (Box 150, Folder 3)
      - Correspondence, legislation. no date (Box 150, Folder 4)
      - Correspondence, Arizona Cattle Growers' Association. no date (Box 150, Folder 5)
      - Correspondence, Verde River and Irrigation District. no date (Box 150, Folder 6)
      - Correspondence, Veterans Hospitals, Tucson & Whipple. no date (Box 150, Folder 7)
      - Correspondence, Calvin Coolidge and Dedication of Coolidge Dam. January-March 1930 (Box 150, Folder 8)
      - Correspondence, Bob Thomas, logs of water and oil wells. no date (Box 150, Folder 9)
      - Speeches, National Democratic Club. April 20, 1929 (Box 150, Folder 10)
      - Speeches, 5th Women's Patriotic Conference on National Defense. January 29, 1930 (Box 150, Folder 11)
      - Speeches, National Broadcasting Company. June 8, 1930 (Box 150, Folder 12)
      - Speeches, 6th Women's Patriotic Conference on National Defense. January 29-31, 1931 (Box 150, Folder 13)
      - Department of Agriculture, correspondence. no date (Box 151, Folder 1)
      - Department of Agriculture, Bureau of public roads. no date (Box 151, Folder 2)
      - Department of Agriculture, Forest Service (Smelley case). no date (Box 151, Folder 3)
      - Department of Agriculture, Forest Service (roads). no date (Box 151, Folder 4)
      - Department of Agriculture, Forest Service (various). no date (Box 151, Folder 5)
      - Department of Commerce, Bureau of the Census. no date (Box 151, Folder 6)
      - Department of Labor, Bureau of Immigration and Naturalization. no date (Box 151, Folder 7)
      - Department of Justice. no date (Box 151, Folder 8)
      - Department of the Treasury. no date (Box 151, Folder 9)
      - War Department, removal of Troops from Camp Jones & Camp Little. no date (Box 151, Folder 10)
      - War Department, various. no date (Box 151, Folder 11)
      - Department of Interior, Office of Indian Affairs. no date (Box 152, Folder 1)
      - Department of the Interior, Office of Indian Affairs. no date (Box 152, Folder 2)
      - Department of the Interior, General Land Office (Homestead Lands). no date (Box 152, Folder 3)
      - Department of the Interior, General Land Office (oil and gas permits; stock driveway). no date (Box 152, Folder 4)
      - Department of the Interior, General Land Office (recreation area in Pima County). no date (Box 152, Folder 5)
      - Department of the Interior, General Land Office (House Rock Valley Game Refuge). no date (Box 152, Folder 6)
      - Department of the Interior, General Land Office (pipeline from Mt. Trumbull to Big Springs). no date (Box 152, Folder 7)
      - Department of the Interior, General Land Office (Peterson vs. Curtis; Land at Apache Junction). no date (Box 152, Folder 8)
      - National Park Service (Restoration of Tumacacori Mission). no date (Box 152, Folder 9)
      - Post Office, Correspondence. no date (Box 153, Folder 1)
      - Post Office, Correspondence. no date (Box 153, Folder 2)
      - Post Office, Arizona Post Offices. no date (Box 153, Folder 3-4)
      - Post Office, Southern Airway Route (correspondence). January 1929-March 1931 (Box 153, Folder 5-7)
      - Post Office, Southern Airway Route (photos, maps, clippings, etc). no date (Box 153, Folder 8)
      - Post Office, mail contracts (Pickwick Airways). no date (Box 153, Folder 9)
      - Post Office, mail contracts (various). no date (Box 153, Folder 10)
      - Post Office, miscellaneous material. no date (Box 153, Folder 11)
      - Veterans Bureau. no date (Box 154, Folder 1)
      - Committee on the conservation and administration of the public domain. no date (Box 154, Folder 2)
      - General and Special Claims Commission (various cases). no date (Box 154, Folder 3)
      - General and Special Claims Commission. no date (Box 154, Folder 4)
      - International Joint Boundary Commission (Trail Smelter Case). no date (Box 154, Folder 5)
      - Miscellaneous Commissions. no date (Box 154, Folder 6)
      - Federal Farm Board (miscellaneous correspondence). no date (Box 154, Folder 7)
      - Federal Farm Board (applications for loans, Roosevelt Hay Growers). no date (Box 154, Folder 8)
    - 71st Congress, Legislation, 1929-1931
      - LWD, 71st Congress, Legislative Record. no date (Box 155, Folder 1)
      - LWD's Bills. no date (Box 155, Folder 2-45)
      - Carl Hayden, 71st Congress, Legislative Record. no date (Box 155, Folder 46)
      - Henry F. Ashurst, 71st Congress, Legislative Record. no date (Box 155, Folder 47)
      - Colorado River (bills, appropriations, etc). no date (Box 156, Folder 1)
      - Colorado River, opinions. no date (Box 156, Folder 2)
      - Colorado River, miscellaneous memoranda. no date (Box 156, Folder 3)
      - Colorado River, U.S. Supreme Court Documents. no date (Box 156, Folder 4-5)
      - Colorado River, specifications for construction. no date (Box 156, Folder 6-7)
      - Colorado River, correspondence (general). no date (Box 157, Folder 1-3)
      - Colorado River, correspondence (Carl Hayden). no date (Box 157, Folder 4)
      - Colorado River, correspondence (W.C. Mullendore). no date (Box 157, Folder 5)
      - Colorado River, correspondence (John Mason Ross). no date (Box 157, Folder 6)
      - Colorado River, correspondence (Ray Lyman Wilbur, Secretary of the Interior). no date (Box 157, Folder 7)
      - Colorado River, correspondence (A.H. Favour, John P. Gray, G.E.P. Smith). no date (Box 157, Folder 8)
      - Colorado River, correspondence (Regarding LWD speeches in Congressional Record). no date (Box 157, Folder 9)
      - Colorado River, correspondence (J.E. Curry, Apache Power Company). no date (Box 157, Folder 10)
      - Colorado River, correspondence (regarding jobs on Hoover Dam Project). no date (Box 157, Folder 11)
      - Colorado River, LWD's notes, background material, etc. no date (Box 158, Folder 1-2)
      - Colorado River, contracts. no date (Box 158, Folder 3)
      - Colorado River, reprints, publications. no date (Box 158, Folder 4-5)
      - Colorado River, miscellaneous material. no date (Box 158, Folder 6)
      - Colorado River, clippings. April 1929-February 1931 (Box 159, Folder 1-4)
      - Muscle Shoals, bills, resolutions, reports (Senate). no date (Box 160, Folder 1)
      - Muscle Shoals, bills, resolutions, reports (House). no date (Box 160, Folder 2)
      - Muscle Shoals, H.R. 11585 (drafts, notes, etc). no date (Box 160, Folder 3)
      - Muscle Shoals, correspondence (National Fertilizer Association). no date (Box 160, Folder 4)
      - Muscle Shoals, correspondence (general). no date (Box 160, Folder 5-6)
      - Muscle Shoals, hearings before the Committee on Military Affairs, House of Representatives, 71st Congress, 2nd Session. February 6-April 11, 1930 (Box 160)
      - Muscle Shoals, miscellaneous maps and charts. no date (Box 161, Folder 1)
      - Muscle Shoals, miscellaneous publications, clippings. no date (Box 161, Folder 2)
      - Muscle Shoals, Congressional Record. no date (Box 161, Folder 3)
      - Muscle Shoals, 13 blueprints. no date (Box 161)
      - Irrigation, Parker-Gila Project. no date (Box 162, Folder 1)
      - Irrigation, San Carlos Project (correspondence). April 1929-April 1931 (Box 162, Folder 2-5)
      - Irrigation, San Carlos Project (clippings). no date (Box 162, Folder 6)
      - Irrigation, Smith-Glenn Bill (bills, miscellaneous material). no date (Box 162, Folder 7)
      - Irrigation, Smith-Glenn Bill (correspondence). no date (Box 162, Folder 8)
      - Irrigation, Yuma Mesa Project (correspondence). January 1929-March 1931 (Box 162, Folder 9-10)
      - Tariff, correspondence. no date (Box 163, Folder 1)
      - Tariff, speeches in Congress. no date (Box 163, Folder 2)
      - Tariff, Tariff Act and Amendments. no date (Box 163, Folder 3)
      - Tariff, clippings. no date (Box 163, Folder 4)
      - Tariff, miscellaneous publications. no date (Box 163, Folder 5)
      - Tariff, agricultural products (correspondence). no date (Box 163, Folder 6)
      - Tariff, agricultural products (bills, clippings, miscellaneous material). no date (Box 163, Folder 7)
      - Tariff, cattle and hides. no date (Box 163, Folder 8)
      - Tariff, cotton and jute. no date (Box 163, Folder 9)
      - Tariff, lumber and shingles. no date (Box 164, Folder 1-3)
      - Tariff, ores and metals (copper). no date (Box 164, Folder 4)
      - Tariff, ores and metals (manganese). no date (Box 164, Folder 5)
      - Tariff, ores and metals (various). no date (Box 164, Folder 6)
      - Tariff, oils and fats. no date (Box 165, Folder 1)
      - Tariff, petroleum and crude oil. no date (Box 165, Folder 2)
      - Tariff, sugar. no date (Box 165, Folder 3)
      - Tariff, wool. no date (Box 165, Folder 4)
      - Tariff, miscellaneous. no date (Box 165, Folder 5)
      - Veterans, correspondence. no date (Box 165, Folder 6)
      - Veterans, bills. no date (Box 165, Folder 7)
      - Veterans, "Rankin Bill." no date (Box 165, Folder 8)
      - Veterans, payment of Adjusted Service Certificates (bills, clippings). no date (Box 166, Folder 1)
      - Veterans, payment of Adjusted Service Certificates (hearings). no date (Box 166, Folder 2)
      - Veterans, payment of Adjusted Service Certificates (correspondence). no date (Box 166, Folder 3-4)